ccsoft.ru 2019-08-23

# Bear games - Your Outsourcing Team!

Bear Games ("Company" or "we") are dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our online users and clients ("users" or "you"). This Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") has been crafted to inform you as to the ways we collect, store, use, manage, and, in certain circumstances, share the information you provide in connection with any Company game, application or other our services ("Service"). Please note that the scope of this Privacy Policy is limited to only information collected from Company through use of the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may amend the Privacy Policy from time to time, and we encourage you to consult the Privacy Policy regularly for changes. 

### _Information Collected and Used_

Company's primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the Service and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the Service. When you install any of the Company games, applications or use our website, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through social or mobile network(s) ("network(s)") in accordance with the policies and terms of social and mobile network(s) or our website in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The types of personal information collected in accordance with the activities listed above may vary depending on the activity. This "personal information" is defined as information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. Personal information may include: (1) your first and last name, (2) your profile picture or its URL, (3) your user identification number of the pertinent social or mobile network, which is linked to publicly available information such as name and profile picture (4) the login email you provided to the pertinent social or mobile network upon registration. Additionally, we may acquire information from you through (1) your access and participation in message boards on the Service (2) your email of a question to our customer support (3) your purchase of a virtual product of any type. Please note that because a third-party site manages the purchases of virtual goods offered by the Service, we do not have access to your credit card details and billing information. Company may also invite you to share information about yourself which may include but is not limited to: (1) your age or date of birth; (2) your gender; (3) information about the hardware you may own; (4) your favorite websites and fan pages; (5) your physical location and that of your access device. Company may combine information about you in an attempt to provide you with a better user experience, to improve the quality and value of the Services and to analyze how our Service is used. The Service will also record game play information such as your high scores or game session duration. In addition to information collected as described above, you may choose to share additional information about yourself throughout the Service, such as in games or on message boards. Any actions you perform with other players are considered public and are at your sole discretion. The personal information you provide us will allow us to fulfill your service order, alert of new services, features, or enhancements, handle/route your customer service or technical support questions or issues. We may use your name, profile picture, email address and other information to notify you of new product releases, service notifications, and to solicit your feedback and input. Those emails will contain links for preference management and where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further emails. Finally, any time you access the Service, we may collect aggregate information including but not limited to internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of this activity ("aggregate information"). We use this aggregate information to better tailor the Service to your interests, to provide you more efficient customer support, and to overall enhance the Service. From time to time, we may also post users or clients testimonials that contain personally identifiable information on our website. However, we will obtain the customer’s consent to post these testimonials prior to publication in accordance with the applicable Company agreement. In all cases of data access and collection, the information you provide will not be disclosed, rented, leased, loaned, sold, or otherwise voluntarily distributed to unaffiliated third parties and will be used solely for the purpose of providing you with and improving the Service. 

### _Other Disclosure of Your Personal Information_

You understand and agree that we may be required to disclose any personal information if required to do so by law or in good faith believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process, including but not limited to a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect our rights and property, or that of the public. Note that Company is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that Company may receive. Additionally, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, customer information may be transferred to Company's successor or assignee, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law. 

### _Cookies_

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk, generally to quickly identify a user's computer and to "remember" things about the user's visit, such as your preferences or a user name and password. The Service sends cookies to your computer when you access or view content of a Company game or website. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personal information for purposes such as improving the quality of our service, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the Service easier to use. You can disable cookies at any time, although you may not be able to access or use features of the Service. 

### _Links_

The Service may contain links to other websites. The fact that the Service links to a website or presents a banner ad or other type of advertisement does not mean that Company endorses or authorizes that third party, nor is it a representation of our affiliation with that third party. Company is in no way responsible for the privacy policies of these other websites to which you chose to access from the Service. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of those websites when exiting the Service. 

### _Third-Party Advertising Companies_

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Service. We do not provide any personal information to third-party advertising companies on a non-aggregate basis. Our system and the third-party advertising technology may use aggregate information, non-personal information, Company's cookies on your hard drive and your use of the Service to target advertisements. In addition, advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on other sites. Third-party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags (also called "clear gifs" or "beacons") to help manage and optimize online advertising. Beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which is beacon is located, and to learn which banner ads bring users to a given site. 

### _Changing or Deleting Your Information_

You may review, update, correct or delete any personal information by changing the applicable information in your profile page on social or mobile network(s) or other gathered information. If you completely delete all this information, your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us. 

### _Security_

We have put in place reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

### _Policy Regarding Children_

The Service is not geared toward children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information we will delete such information from our files as quickly as possible. 

### _Contacting Us_

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@beargg.com.
